So far, with functions, we have seen
how to call a function and use arguments
within a function. In Python, you can set
default values for function arguments,
which will be used if the caller does
not provide a value for them. Sometimes,
an argument may use a default value, such as
when a sales tax rate is one predominant rate or,
in the case of gaming and this 422-default file,
the usual multiplier on a score is 1.5. So,
to save time and potential errors in calling
functions, we could make 1.5 the default value
for the multiplier argument. To make that happen,
I will go to the function definition on line 1 and
type equal sign 1.5 after the multiplier
argument. Then, to test this, on line 4,
I will remove the second argument from the
function call. I will run the code, and the
first print score is perfect as it took the 3000
and multiplied it by 1.5. Though not common for
smaller functions, one could specify the order
of the arguments used when calling a function.
The use of default and keyword arguments often
depends on the function's complexity and purpose,
not necessarily its size. To illustrate this
concept, I will add another print statement
on line 6 that calls the total score function,
specifying the name and value of each argument as
keyword arguments. A developer may use this method
of calling a function to either be more specific
about displaying which arguments are being used
or perhaps because the data needed for a function
are listed on a form in this order. Whatever
the case may be, I will rerun this code, and
the function returns three total scores, all with
the function called in slightly different ways.